adcommunal.net 2014-08-01

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy:

At Ad Communal Inc, we are committed to protecting your privacy, and we strive to keep sensitive and personal information confidential. We suggest that all affiliates and merchants/advertisers read this policy in order to better understand how the information you provide to us and that we may otherwise collect may be used. If you have any queries relating to this policy, please do not hesitate to contact us at [info@adcommunal.com](mailto:info@adcommunal.com) . By accessing the Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY OR THE ACCEPTABLE USE POLICY PROVIDED ON THIS SITE, PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO AD COMMUNAL INC. OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEBSITES REFERRED TO IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

Please note that our privacy policy changes from time to time, and the changes are effective upon posting. Please check back frequently for updates as it is your sole responsibility to be aware of changes. Ad Communal Inc. does not provide any notices of changes in any manner other than by posting the changes at this website. The continued use of the Site after such modification or amendments constitutes acceptance of such modifications or amendments.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY OR THE ACCEPTABLE USE POLICY PROVIDED ON THIS SITE, PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO AD COMMUNAL INC. OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEBSITES REFERRED TO IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

When you register and start using any of our sites located at www.AdCommunal.com (the "Site"), we require relevant program information, including but not limited to log-in, contact, company, website, website user and payment data in order to manage your account and provide you with the services requested. In addition once you are a member of Ad Communal Inc., we require sales and earnings data, and we collect performance statistics related to your Ad Communal Inc. affiliate program(s) in order to properly compensate our users. 

**Contacting us with a question:** When you contact us with a question or suggestion, we may collect your name, e-mail address and any comments you have. We only use this information to respond to and/or resolve your question or concern.

**Information collected by Cookies and Web Beacons, etc.**

(a) Ad Communal uses cookies to enable you to sign in to certain services and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web server. Some cookies are used only to assist you with your session on a Website – such cookies expire automatically after you terminate your session. Ad Communal also uses cookies to improve the sign-in experience on certain Websites. For example, your user ID may be stored in a cookie that will remain on your computer after you terminate your session. This cookie allows your user ID to be pre-populated, so that you will only need to type your password the next time you sign in. Finally, Ad Communal may place a cookie on your hard disk on behalf of a sponsor when such sponsor’s web page is shown, so that the sponsor can measure the effectiveness of such web page. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies can only be accessed or read by the domain that placed them. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use certain features of a Website that depend on cookies. 

(b) Web Beacons:   
A web beacon is a programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page, but can also be used to transfer your unique user identification to a database and associate you with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows AD COMMUNAL INC. to track certain websites you visit. Web beacons are used to track AD COMMUNAL INC. behavioral habits for marketing purposes to determine products or services with which you may be interested. In addition to using web beacons on web pages, AD COMMUNAL INC. also uses web beacons in email messages sent to individuals listed in AD COMMUNAL INC.'s database.

(c) IP Addresses:   
AD COMMUNAL INC. automatically tracks certain information based upon your behavior on the Site. We may use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the site or not), your computer browser information, and your Internet Protocol address. Your Internet Protocol ("IP") address is a unique Internet "address" which is assigned to you by your Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). For local area network ("LAN"), DSL, or cable modem users, an IP address may be permanently assigned to a particular computer. IP addresses are automatically logged by Web servers, collecting information about a user's traffic patterns. While the IP address does not identify an individual by name, it may, with the cooperation of the ISP, be used to locate and identify an individual using the Web. Your IP address can, however, reveal what geographic area you are connecting from, or which ISP you are using. Finally, other websites you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those websites and their pages.

(d) Computer Profiles:   
AD COMMUNAL INC. may also collect and accumulate other anonymous data which will help us understand and analyze the Internet experience of our visitors. For instance, AD COMMUNAL INC. may accumulate visitor data relating to referring domain names, the type of browsers used, operating system software, screen resolutions, color capabilities, browser plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords and JavaScript enablement. When you provide us with Personal Information, we are able to use such visitor data to identify you.

(e) New Technology:   
The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly developing. As a result, AD COMMUNAL INC. strongly encourages individuals to revisit this Privacy Policy for any updates regarding its use of new technology. 

(f)Third party vendors including DoubleClick and Google, show our ads and advertiser's ads on sites on the internet Third party vendors, including DoubleClick and Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to this website. Users may opt out of Third party, DoubleClick or Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page, the ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)[DoubleClick opt-out page](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx) or the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**User Provided Information**  
User-Provided Information. In order to utilize the services at some Websites you may be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information, including, but not limited to account information (user name and password), email address, IM user ID, name and company name, and home or work address and telephone number, as well as certain demographic information such as city, state, country and zip code (“PII”). Ad Communal uses your PII to deliver the services you have requested and to communicate with you, including certain mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, information on technical service issues, and security announcements. We may also occasionally send you product surveys or promotional mailings to inform you of other products or services available from Ad Communal. All such information is provided voluntarily by you. If you provide a friend’s email address to Ad Communal for the “ambassador referral” feature, we use that email address only for the purpose of sending your friend the email you requested. No PII is utilized by Ad Communal Inc. for the purpose of displaying targeted websites or for profiling.

**When We Disclose Information**  
Ad Communal may use PII for any of the following purposes at our sole discretion including, but not limited to : (a) customer service; (b) marketing; and (c) as necessary to comply with the law. Should Ad Communal Inc. be subject to an acquisition, merger, sale, or other change of control or business entity status, Ad Communal Inc. reserves the right to transfer or assign the Information collected from the website.

3.2. Customer Service:   
AD COMMUNAL INC. will use your Personal Information to respond to you, to process, validate and verify requests and/or purchase orders, to fulfill any of your requests and to tailor your experience on the Site.

3.3. Marketing:   
AD COMMUNAL INC. will use your Personal Information for any marketing and survey purpose on behalf of AD COMMUNAL INC. and its partners to send information to you about additional goods or services that may be of interest to you.

3.4. Complying with Legal Process:   
AD COMMUNAL INC. will use or disclose your Personal Information in response to subpoenas, court orders, warrants, or legal process, or to otherwise establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims or in the event you violate or breach an agreement with AD COMMUNAL INC.. AD COMMUNAL INC. will use and disclose your Personal Information if we believe you will harm the property or rights of AD COMMUNAL INC., its owners, or those of AD COMMUNAL INC. 's other customers. Finally, we will use or disclose your Personal Information if we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of AD COMMUNAL INC.’s Acceptable Use Policy, or as otherwise required by law when responding to subpoenas, court orders and other legal processes.

3.5. Order Fulfillment:   
AD COMMUNAL INC. will transfer your Personal Information to third parties when necessary to provide a product or service that you order from such third party while using the Site or when responding to offers provided by AD COMMUNAL INC..

3.6. Data Summary:   
AD COMMUNAL INC. may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons.

3.7. Other Access to Personal Information:   
You have access to your Personal Information collected by the Site and AD COMMUNAL INC.. You may correct, amend, or delete such Personal Information by logging into your AD COMMUNAL account, or emailing support@adcommunal.com. AD COMMUNAL INC. may also give advertising clients and email services providers access to your email address and IP addresses to verify the origin of the Personal Information collected.

3.8. Data Summary:   
AD COMMUNAL INC. may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons.

**How We Protect Your Information**  
We employ a number of safeguards to protect your information. Every user creates a unique password that only the user knows. You should never share your password and take usual recommended precautions (use a combination of numbers, letters and upper- and lowercase; change your password periodically).

**Minors**  
We do not knowingly solicit information from users under the age of 18 and require all affiliates to certify that they are legal adults, 18 years or older.

**General Notes About Our Privacy Policy**  
Ad Communal Inc. websites contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for their privacy policies and urge you to review their respective policies. 

We are also not responsible for the privacy policies of our partner merchants' and affiliates' sites and advise you to familiarize yourself with their respective policies.

5\. Unsubscribe Procedures.

If you wish to discontinue receiving email messages from AD COMMUNAL INC., you may submit your email address to [optout@AdCommunalInc.com](mailto:optout@AdCommunalInc.com) or the postal address listed below.

Third Party Newsletter – if applicable

By submitting your information you agree to receive a third party newsletter from a selected Ad Communal Inc. Affiliate. There is no cost to receive this newsletter. Should you have any questions or concerns or if you would like to discontinue receipt of the newsletter simply email us at [ newsletter@AdCommunalInc.com](mailto:newsletter@AdCommunalInc.com)

6\. Special Notice to California Residents and California User Consumer Rights.

As a California resident, you have certain rights under state law that relate to the sharing of your Personal Information with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. AD COMMUNAL INC. has chosen to comply with California law SB-27 in the following way:   
First, individual consumers who reside in California and who have provided their Personal Information to AD COMMUNAL INC. may request (no more than once per calendar year) information about our disclosures of certain categories of your Personal Information to any third parties. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [legal@AdCommunal.com](mailto:legal@AdCommunal.com) and provide us with your name, address, and e-mail address. Within thirty days of receiving such a request, AD COMMUNAL INC. will provide a list of categories of Personal Information disclosed to third parties during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of such third parties.

All inquiries relating to California SB-27 should be directed to us at legal@Ad Communal.com.   
Additionally, in accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with the California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 

916-445-1254 or  800-952-5210; or by email to [dca@dca.ca.gov](mailto:dca@dca.ca.gov)

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of AD COMMUNAL INC. please contact us at:   
Ad Communal Inc.   
16 West Main Street   
Christiana, DE   
19702   

302 476 2721
